<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Academy</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bird BOX</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Creed II</item>
        <item>Once Upon a Deadpool</item>
        <item>Dragon</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball Z</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Mary Poppins Returns</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_score">
        <item>75</item>
        <item>68</item>
        <item>83</item>
        <item>70</item>
        <item>81</item>
        <item>65</item>
        <item>67</item>
        <item>69</item>
        <item>80</item>
        <item>65</item>
        <item>63</item>
        <item>66</item>
        <item>89</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rilis">
        <item>5 Oktober 2018</item>
        <item>21 Desember 2018</item>
        <item>25 April 2018</item>
        <item>13 Desember 2018</item>
        <item>24 Oktober 2018</item>
        <item>15 Desember 2018</item>
        <item>21 November 2018</item>
        <item>13 Desember 2018</item>
        <item>11 Desember 2018</item>
        <item>26 April 2018</item>
        <item>16 januari 2019</item>
        <item>19 Oktober 2018</item>
        <item>13 Desember 2018</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.</item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
        <item>lAs the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy</item>
        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics.</item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred</item>
        <item>Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent with ties to his familys past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.</item>
        <item>A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpools PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a Princess Bride-esque story thats full of magic, wonder zero A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpools PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a Princess Bride-esque story thats full of magic, wonder zero</item>
        <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless’ discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball Z is a Japanese animated television series produced by Toei Animation. Dragon Ball Z is the sequel to the Dragon Ball anime and adapts the last 26 volumes of the original 42 volume Dragon Ball manga</item>
        <item>In a series of escalating encounters, former security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb, a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence</item>
        <item>Captain Glass of the USS Arkansas discovers that a coup détat is taking place in Russia, so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.</item>
        <item>In Depression-era London, a now-grown Jane and Michael Banks, along with Michael three children, are visited by the enigmatic Mary Poppins following a personal loss. Through her unique magical skills, and with</item>
    </string-array>


    <array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_marrypopins</item>
    </array>
</resources>
